<Flipbook>
<Card>
<Question>
Which data structure has a time complexity of O(1) for access?
A: Array
B: Singly-Linked List
C: Stack
D: Binary Search Tree
</Question>
<Answer>A</Answer>
</Card>
<Card>
<Question>
Which data structure does NOT have a time complexity of O(N) for search?
A: Singly-Linked List
B: Array
C: Binary Search Tree
D: Stack
</Question>
<Answer>C</Answer>
</Card>
<Card>
<Question>
What is the average time complexity of selection sort?
A: O(n)
B: O(n log(n))
C: O(n+k)
D: O(n^2)
</Question>
<Answer>D</Answer>
</Card>
<Card>
<Question>
What is the average time complexity of quick sort?
A: O(n)
B: O(n log(n))
C: O(n+k)
D: O(n^2)
</Question>
<Answer>B</Answer>
</Card>
<Card>
<Question>
Which data structure has a time complexity of O(1) for deletion?
A: Stack
B: Doubly-Linked list
C: Binary Search Tree
D: Array
</Question>
<Answer>B</Answer>
</Card>
<Card>
<Question>
Which sorting algorithm does NOT have a worst case time complexity of O(n^2)?
A: Quick Sort
B: Selection Sort
C: Insertion Sort
D: Merge Sort
    </Question>
    <Answer>D</Answer>
  </Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which software development methodology is characterized by brief daily meetings between the team leader and team members, along with an extended meeting once every 2-4 weeks?
		</Question>
		<Answer>Scrum</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Of these programming languages, which is characterized by its use of "lazy evaluation?"
			A: Java
			B: Perl
			C: C#
			D: Haskell
		</Question>
		<Answer>D</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which of these statements is TRUE in regards to classes and structs in C++?
			A: The default scope of a struct is public and the default scope of a class is private.
			B: Structs cannot have protected member variables.
			C: Member variables in classes must have their access explicitly defined.
			D: Like their C counterpart, structs in C++ have no concept of encapsulation, so everything is public.
		</Question>
		<Answer>A</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Who created C++?
			A: John McCarthy
			B: Bjarne Stroustrup
			C: Dennis Ritchie
			D: Linus Torvalds
		</Question>
		<Answer>B</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			There are three doors. Behind one of them is a prize. Once you pick a door, one of the unpicked doors is revealed to be empty, and you are given the chance to repick. If you repick, does your chance of winning increase?
		</Question>
		<Answer>Yes</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which one of these codenames has not been a name for any of Intel's processor microarchitectures?
			A: Nehalem
			B: Thuban
			C: Skylake
			D: Devil's Canyon
		</Question>
		<Answer>B</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Of these GPU microarchitectures, which was notorious for extremely high load temperatures?
			A: Tahiti (Radeon 7000 Series)
		        B: Kepler (GeForce 600, 700 Series)
			C: Evergreen (Radeon 5000 Series)
			D: Fermi (GeForce 400 Series)
		</Question>
		<Answer>D</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which one of these software development methodologies is known for using "story" cards with scenarios on them describing different requirements?
			A: Scrum
			B: Rational Unified Process
			C: Extreme Programming
			D: Waterfall
		</Question>
		<Answer>C</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which of these requirements is not generally considered a non-functional requirement?
			A: Performance
			B: Security
			C: Compliance
			D: None of the above
		</Question>
		<Answer>D</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which weather cloud type is usually a sign of impending thunderstorms?
			A: Cumulonimbus clouds
			B: Stratus clouds
			C: Cumulus clouds
			D: Altocirrus clouds
		</Question>
		<Answer>A</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Who usually teaches CSCI 176 (parallel processing) at Fresno State?
			A: Dr. Jin Park
			B: Dr. David Ruby
			C: Dr. Ming Li
			D: Dr. Shih-Hsi (Alex) Liu
		</Question>
		<Answer>A</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Who was originally supposed to teach CSCI 115 at Fresno State in Spring 2015 before Dr. Wilson was chosen to teach it?
			A: Dr. Henderson Yeung
			B: Dr. Shih-Hsi "Alex" Liu
			C: Dr. Ming Li
			D: Dr. Shigeko Seki
		</Question>
		<Answer>A</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which of the following professors has never been Chair of Computer Science at Fresno State?
			A: Dr. Todd Wilson
			B: Dr. Ming Li
			C: Dr. Jin Park
			D: Dr. Henderson Yeung
		</Question>
		<Answer>C</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which of these species does NOT give live birth?
			A: Emu
			B: Boa Constrictor
			C: Komodo Dragon
			D: Human
		</Question>
		<Answer>C</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			What/who has been the hide-and-seek champion of the world since 1958?
			A: Waldo
			B: Father
			C: The semi-colon when programming
			D: Watson Tungjunyatham
		</Question>
		<Answer>C</Answer>
	</Card>
	<Card>
		<Question>
			Which of these products can you NOT purchase on Amazon?
			A: Depleted uranium
			B: 55 gallons of water-based lubricant
			C: Tobacco
			D: Dead rabbit
		</Question>
		<Answer>C</Answer>
	</Card>
</Flipbook>			






			
